keeping up with the pace of work can be
challenging especially when your
business is adapting and growing
transform the way work gets done with
Microsoft co-pilot in Dynamics 365
business Central your everyday AI
companion save time by asking questions
to find what you
need and onboard quickly with co-pilot
to guide you as you develop new
skills accelerate sales and Spark
creativity with marketing Tech
suggestions tailor to your unique brand
using details already in business
Central like color size and
material use co-pilot to create sales
quotes orders and invoices faster and
easier than ever before so you can
invest time in relationships instead of
paperwork simplify your day-to-day by
automating business processes with power
automate
flows and reclaim time for your most
impactful work by using co-pilot to keep
your finances organized from reconciling
bank statements to matching purchase
orders with e invoices all while using
analysis views to make datadriven
decisions that Propel your business
forward to new levels of
success work smarter adapt faster and
perform better with Microsoft co-pilot
in business Central